Rodolfo Hans S. Silva

Consolação, São Paulo / He, Him

rodolfohans@gmail.com

+55 21 98261-8770

ABOUT ME

I am a Designer with 13 years of experience across the areas of product, UX, marketing and web design. I bring a diverse skill set to my work and I am passionate about creating great experiences, while achieving a balance between user needs and technical feasibility.

PORTFOLIO

rodolfohans.com

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/rodolfohans

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accenture / UX and UI Designer

October 2019 to March 2023

I worked on multiple projects, starting with Banco PAN's vehicle financing team, where I helped streamline the credit analysis process and improved the platform's attractiveness to used car sellers. As a result, its ranking has risen from 4th to 2nd place in small used car sales financing, and design inconsistencies have been resolved to align with the bank's design system.

I also acquired firsthand experience in the water services, telecom, agro, mining, and carbon trading industries, as well as in collaborating with both English and Spanish native speakers.

Key functions:

- Conduct interviews with firsthand users.
- Conduct usability tests and summarize insights.
- Design and refine workflows.
- Design high-fidelity UI.
- Organize design assets.

Nexaas / UI Designer

October 2016 to September 2019

I contributed to the marketing team to highlight the company, its products, and sub-affiliated entities, with a focus on prioritizing the consumer experience (CX) through design for both online and offline mediums. Additionally, I co-led the company rebranding project and collaborated with the product team to refine it's design system.

Key functions:

- Optimizing institutional websites.
- Designing email marketing campaigns and Google ads.
- Creating designs for offline media, such as stands and brochures.
- Improving and organizing sub-brands.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Wink Mídia / Graphic Designer

May 2016 to October 2016

Developed online and offline media focused on the real estate, hospital, and gastronomic sectors. Led art direction for the development of new visual identities.

Key functions:

- Optimizing institutional websites.
- Designing email marketing campaigns and Google ads.
- · Creating designs for offline media.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Game Artist

EBAC / 2023 / Ongoing

Android Developer

Instituto Infnet / 2015 / 128 hours

Bachelor in Video Game Design

Universidade Estácio de Sá / 2014 to 2015 / Discontinued

Bachelor in Industrial Design

Universidade Estácio de Sá / 2006 to 2011

SKILLS

Proficient in:

- UX discovery methodologies
- UI design and process documentation
- UI validations

Currently studying:

- Game mechanics
- UI design applied to games
- Concept art design
- 3D modeling

Others:

- Image manipulation
- Vectorial illustration
- Motion graphics notion
- Editorial design
- HTML, CSS and JS notion